DexHand Data Collector
24-DOF Five-Finger Dexterous Hand
Core Innovation: 4ms Slip Recovery
SlipZero Controller - Faster than Third Place
Vision-Tactile Fusion Control
30Hz Vision + 250Hz Tactile = 100% Success
Detection: < 1ms | Recovery: 4ms
Control Frequency: 250Hz
Task 1-4: Basic Grasping & Placement
Tri-Finger, Five-Finger, Cap Rotation, Placement
Task 5-8: Advanced Manipulation
Handoff, Tool Use, Gravity, Soft Objects
Task 9-12: Complex Scenarios
Multi-Object Sort, Adaptive, Triage, Slip Recovery
Performance: 12/12 tasks, 100% success rate
Total Tests: 204/204
Real Hardware: ESP32 Serial Validation
24 DOF | 19 Actuators | 64 Sensors
Industrial Applications:
Medical Robotics, Pharmaceutical Handling
UUID: 438a8329-a02c-4fdb-80b5-12bff9d9f69d
FFAI Robothon 2026 - DexHand Category